We are not armed.
Get up.
Leave!
HALT!
I am pregnant.
What are you doing here?
Are you American?
Hungry. We're all hungry.
Really? Are you hungry?
Who are you?
Hmm?
Where do you get this?
It belonged to her mother.
No.
You have three seconds to tell me
where you got it.
Huh? One!
Two!
Three!
I have the same necklace!
Where did you get it?
Where did you get this?
What do you know?
I'm untying you because I believe
that you, Hans Neumann, are my father,
and that I am your daughter.
I'm going to trust you,
and I can only hope
that you learn to trust us too.
Don't come any closer.
I don't want to hurt any of you.
Let me go,
so I can follow my orders.
Halt!
Don't come any closer.
If you go through with your mission,
you will die, and when you die,
you will be responsible
for our destinies.
I must complete my mission.
I'm not a Nazi! I'm a soldier!
Get out of my way!
We have to go to the bunker.
If you die, she dies.
My mother, your wife.
Do you understand?
Save yourself for her. For me.
Hurry!